[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Which is an alternative term for backpacking?",
    "answer": "D",
    "reward": 500
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Which is NOT a component of a canoe?",
    "answer": "C",
    "reward": 1000
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the shape of a 'tipi' tent?",
    "answer": "B",
    "reward": 2000
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "The Hollywood movie 'Vertical Limit' begins with which outdoor activity?",
    "answer": "A",
    "reward": 4000
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the term used for 'climbing urban structures'?",
    "answer": "A",
    "reward": 8000
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which is the highest class of river where rafting is almost impossible?",
    "answer": "A",
    "reward": 16000
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "In which part of the world is hunting referred to as 'shikar'?",
    "answer": "B",
    "reward": 32000
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "For which outdoor activity would you need a sinker, gaff, and rod?",
    "answer": "B",
    "reward": 64000
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Paul Edward Yost is referred to as the 'Father' of which outdoor activity?",
    "answer": "B",
    "reward": 125000
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is an alternative name for Boutique Camping?",
    "answer": "A",
    "reward": 250000
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a category of mountain biking?",
    "answer": "B",
    "reward": 500000
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Which outdoor activity is also known as 'spelunking' in the US and 'potholing' in the UK?",
    "answer": "D",
    "reward": 1000000
  }
]
